[
  {
    "Category":"Mad God Munchies",
    "Clues": [
      {
        "Question": "This consumable allows you to move with haste...but only temporarily!",
        "Answer": "Speed Sprout"
      },
      {
        "Question": "You won't need an ID to enter this alcohol-centric venue, but you will need this consumable!",
        "Answer": "Wine Cellar Incantation"
      },
      {
        "Question": "Things look a little unusual when you're under the influence of this consumable",
        "Answer": "Magic Mushroom"
      },
      {
        "Question": "We've all had sugar rushes in the past, but none quite as explosive as this consumable candy",
        "Answer": "Rock Candy"
      },
      {
        "Question": "It's a fountain...no, a priest...no, simply a player using this consumable",
        "Answer": "Snake Oil"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "Category":"Rocket-Driven Cars",
    "Clues":[
      {
        "Question":"This flammable chemical shares its name with the game's most used car",
        "Answer":"Octane"
      },
      {
        "Question":"The Mount Champion topper hails from the original RLCS fan rewards, and stands as a nod to this player",
        "Answer":"Kronovi"
      },
      {
        "Question":"This notorious Batmobile player is famous for both his airdribble double touch, and as the first substitute to win RLCS",
        "Answer":"0ver Zer0"
      },
      {
        "Question":"Owned by only this many players, the Season 1 Platinum Crown Topper is certainly sight to behold",
        "Answer":"100"
      },
      {
        "Question":"It's rare to be on the receiving end of a ceiling shot, but SquishyMuffinz famously managed one against this RLCS team during a match",
        "Answer":"Method"
      }
    ]
  }
]